Can you guys build on a budget,
with no bells and whistles?
Because people think we can't do that.
Of course we can, but let's be honest.
Nobody wants to build with
standardized materials.
If I say, let's carpet the bedrooms
upstairs, it's like I said a four-letter
word. It's like, you know. The minute
you said carpet, that needs to be...
Nobody wants to see carpet. Now, this new
thing with these white oak floors, and
six- and seven-inch floors.
I mean, it's crazy numbers.
When you start pricing out seven-inch
white oak floors, you can't even go with
real white oak anymore. The price is crazy.
So we go engineered. Even the
engineered is up in the $7, $8 range
for that, unfinished. You know, we
could definitely build on standard. You
just have to know, you've got to come clean
and tell us what you really want. And not
to say that once we start standard and
you want options, we'll put all the
options out there for you, and then it's up to
the client to decide. Yeah, I mean,
this is your standard Fabuwood kitchen, which is
middle of the line. You can go with a
builder's line, which we can make look just
as good. It's an import, but nobody, you
know, everybody tends to pull away from
the import line. Or you can go full
custom, where we custom build all your
cabinets, any wood species you want,
inset doors. But, you know, then you're
talking about increasing the budgets.
You know, if you're a client looking to just
get some extra room, put your four
kids upstairs, get the five bedrooms,
you don't have to go nine-foot ceilings.
You could just get that square footage
you want, keep everything down to a
minimum, and then you can always
add that stuff later, right?
That's right. That's right.